<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<article article-type="research-article" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
    xmlns="http://jats.nlm.nih.gov" xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://jats.nlm.nih.gov/publishing/1.0/JATS-journalpublishing1.xsd">
    <front>
        <journal-meta>
            <publisher>
                <publisher-name>American Association for the Advancement of Science</publisher-name>
                <publisher-loc>New York, USA</publisher-loc>
            </publisher>
        </journal-meta>
        <article-meta>
            <conference>AAAS</conference>
            <title-group>
                <article-title>Chicken Chicken Chicken</article-title>
                <subtitle>Chicken Chicken</subtitle>
            </title-group>
            <contrib-group>
                <contrib contrib-type="author">
                    <name>
                        <surname>Zongker</surname>
                        <given-names>Doug</given-names>
                    </name>
                    <aff>
                        <institution content-type="edu">University of Washington</institution>
                    </aff>
                </contrib>
            </contrib-group>
        </article-meta>
        <abstract>
            <label>Chicken</label>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                <italic>chicken</italic> chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken. Chicken, chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken, chicken
                chicken chicken “chicken chicken” chicken “chicken chicken” chicken. Chicken, chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken (chicken chicken) chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken.</p>
        </abstract>
        <notes>
            <note><label>CC Chickens:</label> C.3.2 [Chickens]: Chicken Chickens—chicken/chicken
                chicken; C.3.4 [Chicken chicken]: Chicken chicken chicken—chickens; C.2.4
                [Chicken-chicken chickens]: Chicken/Chicken, chicken chickens</note>
        </notes>
        <kwd-group kwd-group-type="author-created"><label>Chickens:</label>
            <kwd>chicken</kwd>, <kwd>chicken chicken</kwd>, <kwd>chicken</kwd>,
            <kwd>chicken</kwd></kwd-group>
    </front>
    <body>
        <sec disp-label="1">
            <label>1</label>
            <title>Chicken</title>
            <p>Chicken chicken, chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken  <xref type="ref" rid="ref4">[4]</xref> . Chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken:
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. (chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken!)</p>
            <p>Chicken, chicken-chicken chicken chicken—chicken chicken, chicken chicken 95% chicken
                chicken-chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken—chicken chicken chicken
                chicken. Chicken, chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken 1987. Chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken-chicken-chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken,
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken, chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken (chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken).</p>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken (chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken) chicken chicken chickens chicken. Chicken chickens chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken “chicken” chicken chickens chicken. Chicken chicken,
                chicken-chicken chicken chickens, chicken chicken chicken<xref ref-type="footnote"
                    rid="fn1">1</xref> Chicken chicken’s “chicken” chicken chicken chicken chicken.
                chicken chicken chicken chicken—chicken chicken <italic>chicken</italic> chicken chicken
                chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken.</p>
            <fig id="fg1" position="float">
                <label>Chicken 1</label>
                <caption>Chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken, chicken chicken (chicken chicken
                    chicken) chicken chicken-chicken. </caption>
            </fig>
            <fig id="fg2" position="float">
                <label>Chicken 2</label>
                <caption>Chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken,chicken chicken chicken chicken,
                    chicken chicken chicken chicken.</caption>
            </fig>
            <fig id="fg3" position="float">
                <label>Chicken 3</label>
                <caption>Chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken-chicken chickens chickens.</caption>
            </fig>
            <fig id="fg4" position="float">
                <label>Chicken 4</label>
                <caption>Chicken chicken 2, 4, 8, chicken 16 chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken,
                    chicken chicken (p.p., chicken-chicken) chickens chicken.</caption>
            </fig>
            <fngroup>
                <fn id="fn1"><label>1</label> Chicken chicken chicken chicken <italic>chicken chicken</italic> chicken;
                    chicken chickens. Chicken chicken Chicken  <xref type="ref" rid="ref5">[5]</xref> .</fn>
            </fngroup>
        </sec>
        <sec>
            <label>2</label>
            <title>Chicken chicken</title>
            <p> Chicken chicken chicken, C(<italic>n</italic>) chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                <xref type="ref" rid="ref4">[4]</xref> . Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken’s chickens Chicken  <xref type="ref" rid="ref3">[3]</xref>  chicken chicken,
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken
                chickens chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken-chicken chicken chicken Chicken
                <italic>p. pu</italic>  <xref type="ref" rid="ref3">[3]</xref>  chicken chickens chicken  <xref type="ref" rid="ref2">[2]</xref> , chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chickens.</p>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken—chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken C(log <italic>n</italic>)  <xref type="ref" rid="ref2">[2]</xref> .
                Chicken <italic>p. pu</italic>  <xref type="ref" rid="ref4">[4]</xref>  chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken-chicken chicken.</p>
            <p>Chicken, chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chickenchicken chicken, chicken,
                chicken chicken chicken chicken C(1), chicken chicken chicken chicken [3, 5]. Chicken
                chicken  <xref type="ref" rid="ref2">[2]</xref> , chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken, chicken-chicken, chicken-chicken chicken  <xref type="ref" rid="ref1">[1]</xref>  chicken chicken
                chicken chicken.</p>
        </sec>
        <sec>
            <label>3</label>
            <title>Chicken</title>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chickens
                <italic>chicken</italic> chicken chickens. Chicken chicken chicken 1. Chicken
                chicken chicken chickens chicken; chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken
                chicken, chicken chickens chicken chicken chicken.</p>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken.
                Chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chickens chicken chickens chicken chicken, chicken “chicken chicken chicken chicken”
                chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken.</p>
            <p>Chicken, chicken chicken chicken: <disp-formula id="eq1"
                ><label>(1)</label></disp-formula> chicken <disp-formula id="blockeq1"/>
            </p>
            <p>Chicken chicken CCC chicken, chicken <inline-formula/>. Chickens chickens chickens
                chickens. Chicken chicken, chickens chicken chicken chicken chckens. Chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken <inline-formula/> chicken chickens chicken, chicken
                chickens chickens chickens <inline-formula/>.</p>
            <p>Chicken, chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken <disp-formula id="eq2"
                ><label>(2)</label></disp-formula>
            </p>
            <p>Chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken-chicken chicken
                chicken chicken. Chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken,
                chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken
                chicken chicken.</p>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chickens
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chickens
                chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chickens chi-
                cken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken, chicken
                chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken, chicken chicken
                chicken chicken. Chicken chicken CCC chicken chickens chicken chicken, chicken chickens
                chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken
                chicken chicken—chicken chicken chicken, chicken’s chicken chicken chicken. Chicken
                chicken chicken chicken (chicken <xref type="figure" rid="fg3">Chicken 3</xref>) chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken—chicken chicken (chicken-chicken, chicken chicken) chicken (chicken chicken,
                chicken).</p>
            
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken.
                Chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken “chicken chicken” chicken chicken, chicken “chicken chicken chicken chicken”
                chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken-chicken chicken chicken chicken.</p>
        </sec>
        <sec>
            <label>4</label>
            <title>Chicken chicken chicken</title>
            <p>Chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken—chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken <italic>chicken</italic> chicken. Chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken, chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken “chicken” chicken chicken (p.p., chicken chicken,
                chicken <italic>chicken</italic>!)</p>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken <xref type="figure" rid="fg4">Chicken 4</xref>. Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken.
                <xref type="table" rid="tb1">Chicken 1</xref> chicken chicken chicken chickens, chickens chickenchicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken (chicken/chicken chicken) chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken,
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken (chicken, chicken chicken, chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken). Chicken
                chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken
                chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken.</p>
            <p>Chicken chicken chicken; chicken chickens chicken:</p>
            <list list-type="bullet">
                <list-item>
                    <title>Chicken chicken chicken.</title>
                    <p>Chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken, chicken chicken. Chicken, chicken
                        chickens chicken.</p>
                </list-item>
                <list-item>
                    <title>Chicken.</title>
                    <p>Chickens chickens chickens; chicken chicken chicken chicken  <xref type="ref" rid="ref4">[4]</xref> . Chicken
                        chicken chickens chicken— chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken chickens.</p>
                </list-item>
                <list-item>
                    <title>Chicken chicken chicken.</title>
                    <p>Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken (chicken
                        chicken chickens) chickens chicken chickens chicken. Chicken chickens chicken
                        chicken chicken chicken chicken “chicken” chicken chickens chicken. Chicken
                        chicken, chicken-chicken chicken chickens, chicken chicken chicken chicken
                        chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken’s “chicken” chicken chicken chicken
                        chicken—chicken chicken <italic>chicken</italic> chicken chicken chicken,
                        chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken.</p>
                </list-item>
            </list>
            <p>Chicken chicken, chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chickens
                68,700 chicken chickens chicken. Chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken
                chicken: chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken’s chickens.
                (Chicken chicken.) Chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken;
                chicken chicken-chicken chicken.</p>
            <table-wrap id="tb1" position="float">
                <label>Chicken 1</label>
                <caption>Chicken chicken chicken. Chicken-chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken
                    chicken chicken, chicken chicken chicken chicken, chicken, chicken chicken chicken
                    “chicken” chicken.</caption>
                <table>
                    <thead>
                        <tr>
                            <th>Chicken CH116</th>
                            <th>CH116c</th>
                            <th>CH132</th>
                        </tr>
                    </thead>
                    <tbody>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Chicken</td>
                            <td>57,600</td>
                            <td>57,600</td>
                            <td>68,700</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Ch. Chicken</td>
                            <td>2 × 16</td>
                            <td>2 × 16</td>
                            <td>2 × 32</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Chicken</td>
                            <td>113:1</td>
                            <td>113:1</td>
                            <td>28:1</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Ch CCC</td>
                            <td>0.3463</td>
                            <td>0.3855</td>
                            <td>0.3818</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>chicken</td>
                            <td>-0.039</td>
                            <td>0.0050</td>
                            <td>-0.0015</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>Ch Ch Chick.</td>
                            <td>20.91</td>
                            <td>24.32</td>
                            <td>24.38</td>
                        </tr>
                        <tr>
                            <td>CC</td>
                            <td>9.08ch</td>
                            <td>13.30ch</td>
                            <td>13.40ch</td>
                        </tr>
                    </tbody>
                </table>
            </table-wrap>
        </sec>
    </body>
    <back>
        <ref-list><label>Chickens</label>
            <ref id="ref1"><label>[1]</label> <mixed-citation><name>Chicken</name>. <article-title>Chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken chicken</article-title>. <source>Chicken</source>, <volume>10</volume>(<issue>3</issue>):<fpage>307</fpage>–<lpage>314</lpage>, <year>2000</year>.</mixed-citation></ref>
            <ref id="ref2"><label>[2]</label> <mixed-citation><name>Chicken Chicken</name>. <article-title>Chicken chicken chicken chicken</article-title>. <source>Chicken Chicken Chicken</source>, <volume>12</volume>(<issue>7</issue>):<fpage>629</fpage>–<lpage>639</lpage>, <year>1990</year>.</mixed-citation></ref>
            <ref id="ref3"><label>[3]</label> <mixed-citation><name>Chicken Chicken</name>. <article-title>Chicken: Chicken chicken chicken</article-title>. <source>C. Chicken Chicken</source>, <volume>32</volume>(<issue>35</issue>):<fpage>7164</fpage>–<lpage>7169</lpage>, <year>1993</year>.</mixed-citation></ref>
            <ref id="ref4"><label>[4]</label> <mixed-citation><name>C. Chicken chicken Chicken Chicken</name>. <article-title>Chicken chicken chicken</article-title>. <source>Chicken Chicken Chicken Chicken</source>, <volume>4</volume>(<issue>12</issue>):<fpage>67</fpage>–<lpage>74</lpage>, <year>1995</year>.</mixed-citation></ref>
            <ref id="ref5"><label>[5]</label> <mixed-citation>Chicken chicken Chicken Chicken. <article-title>Chicken chicken chicken</article-title>. <source>Chicken Chicken Chicken Chicken</source>, <volume>15</volume>(<issue>1</issue>):<fpage>542</fpage>–<lpage>546</lpage>, <year>1990</year>.</mixed-citation></ref>
        </ref-list>
    </back>
</article>
